<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://hl7.org/fhir ../../input-cache/schemas/R5/fhir-single.xsd">
  <!-- The spaces between the open and close "a" tag are mandatory.  (Cuz HTML renderers are dumb...) -->
  
	<p class="stu-note">THIS IS A FORKED VERSION!!! THE ORIGINAL VERSION LINK:  <a href="https://simplifier.net/sunwayhie">https://simplifier.net/sunwayhie</a></p>
	
	<a name="intro"> </a>
	<h3>Introduction: Sunway Healthcare Group (SHG)'s Drive for the development and
implementation of a Health Information Exchange (HIE) system</h3>
	<p>
    <strong>Sunway Healthcare Group</strong> is a leading provider of private healthcare in Malaysia, renowned for its comprehensive range of medical services and state-of-the-art facilities. Established in 1999, the Group has grown to include several hospitals and specialty centers across the country, catering to both local and international patients.
	
	Link attached below for our overall SHG Expansion Plan: <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/jessicatan/2024/04/16/malaysian-property-billionaire-jeffrey-cheah-rampsup-healthcare-ambitions-including-seven-new-sunway-hospitals-by-2030/?sh=4f926d9e1c39">https://www.forbes.com/sites/jessicatan/2024/04/16/malaysian-property-billionaire-jeffrey-cheah-rampsup-healthcare-ambitions-including-seven-new-sunway-hospitals-by-2030/?sh=4f926d9e1c39</a>
	</p>	
	
	<a name="objective"> </a>
	<h3>Objective: Establishing a robust Health Information Exchange for data interoperability</h3>
	<p>The primary objective of this project is to establish a robust Health Information Exchange (HIE) that will serve as the backbone for data interoperability within Sunway Healthcare Group. The HIE will ensure the collection and exchange of healthcare data across the organization's network, adhering to universally accepted healthcare data standards. The HIE will empower clinicians with immediate access to patient information, significantly improving clinical decision-making and operational efficiency.
	
	At the same time, the system is also expected to ensure that data collected are standardized and harmonized to form a centralized data warehouse, that lays the foundation framework for various other healthcare data applications beyond HIE from data analytics and integration with patient-facing digital solutions. This comprehensive approach to HIE implementation enables Sunway Healthcare Group to stay at the cutting edge of healthcare innovation, well-equipped for both present needs and future expansions. The successful bidder will provide solutions that not only address the immediate technical specifications but also align with SHG's long-term strategic vision for healthcare excellence.
	</p>	
	
	<a name="contributors"> </a>
	<h3>Author &amp; Contributors</h3>
	<p>
    <table class="regular">
		<thead>
			<tr>
				<th>Role</th>
				<th>Name</th>
				<th>Organization</th>
				<th>Contact</th>
			</tr>
		</thead>
		<tbody>
			<tr>
				<td>Primary Author</td>
				<td>Nguyen Hai Phong</td>
				<td>FPT Corporation</td>
				<td>haiphong.nguyen@gmail.com / phongnh34@fpt.com</td>
			</tr>
		</tbody>
	</table>
	</p>
	
	<p>
	<a name="dependencies"> </a>
	<h3>Dependencies</h3>
	{% include dependency-table.xhtml %}
	</p>
	
	<p>
	<a name="crossversion"> </a>
	<h3>Cross Version Analysis</h3>
	{% include cross-version-analysis.xhtml %}
	</p>
	
	<p>
	<a name="globalprofiles"> </a>
	<h3>Global Profiles</h3>
	{% include globals-table.xhtml %}
	</p>
	
</div>